Happy Yadav is a Data Analytics Intern at Hunar.ai. He has worked with
20+ clients managing over 100,000 data entries. He is passionate about transforming high-volume
hiring through AI. Coding Ninjas CUIET February 2024 - Present. Responsible for managing
all technical projects, coordinating coding initiatives, and providing team support through code reviews
and guidance. Manage the Coding Ninja website built on Firebase and Next.js ensuring
optimal performance and maintenance. FinTrack is a finance management application that allows users
to track, edit, and visualize income and expenses. Leveraged a tech stack of
React, Chart.js, and Tailwind CSS for the frontend, with an Express backend deployed
on Railway and hosted on Vercel. Programming Languages: Python, C++, C, JavaScript, SQL,
HTML, CSS, TypeScript. Libraries and Tools: React, Tailwind, Firebase , Git, Docker, PowerBI,
MySql, Retool.