Policy holders can download Insurance Wallet for one -touch
access. We will not be liable to pay for
the following cases: Your dream two-wheeler. Any loss or
damage caused outside the geographical area. Two Wheeler Package
Policy is designed to ensure that your two-wheeler is
protected when you need it the most. The policy
includes the accidental loss or damage to your two
wheeler caused by any of the following. Bajaj Allianz
General Insurance Company Limited is a joint venture between
Bajaj Finserv Limited and Allanz SE. We will cover
your legal liability arising out of bodily injury to
Bajj AllianZ. 3. Personal Accident Cover for the Occupants
of the Vehicle. 4. Driver, Cleaner or any Workman.
5. Driver or Cleaner of the vehicle. 6. Driver
of the car of any vehicle.